cliftonbank.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy Notice | Community Bank NJ | NJ Banking - Clifton Savings Bank

We know you take online privacy seriously, and so does Clifton Savings Bank (“CSBK”) and its affiliated companies.  We are committed to protecting the personal information of visitors to our company websites, including those found at CliftonSavings.com, CliftonBancorp.com, csbknj.com and Mortgage.Cliftonsavings.com (“Website”). 

The Clifton Saving Bank Website Privacy Policy:

  * Describes the information we collect during your visit to our Websites, including information that you knowingly and voluntarily provide to us.
  * Describes how we may use information about you and/or how you interact with our Website, with whom we share it, and how we protect it. 
  * Describes how we may collect information through the use of cookies and/or other technologies.
  * Describes how we may collect additional information relating to your method of accessing our Website, such as the type of device and browser you are using, the IP address of your device, information about your device's operating system, and additional information associated with your device. 

CSBK offers customers the ability to access their accounts via a login portal on our Website. Customers should be aware that the scope of this policy does NOT include those online or mobile banking services. Instead, when you become a CSBK customer, and annually while you remain a CSBK customer, we will provide you with a Clifton Savings Bank Privacy Notice describing our privacy practices as it relates to your relationship with us. It will describe and provide any updates to the collection and sharing of personal information about our customers, as required by law. Click here for our current Privacy Notice.

You may interact with our Website in a variety of ways, including portable devices (i.e. mobile phone, tablets). We may offer Website or applications that permit browsing and do not require registration or login credentials. 

Our Website may contain links to third party websites not controlled by CSBK or covered by our Website Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy statements of other websites you visit before providing any personal information.

## Acceptance of Clifton Savings Bank Website Privacy Notice

By using CSBK’s Website, you consent to this policy, including your consent to our use and disclosure of information about you in the manner described in this policy.

## What personal information does CSBK collect via its Website?

_If you are just browsing through our Website, we do not request any personally identifiable information, nor do we collect unique identifying information about you_. However, if you send us an email or complete a form, you then voluntarily, and knowingly, provide us your personally identifiable information.

**How does CSBK  use the personal information you provide?**

We use personal information you have provided for various functions, which may include:

  * processing your request for products, services or information
  * improving our customer service and products
  * servicing your account
  * facilitating your participation in online activities

For example, we may use the information you provide when you complete an online application for a product or service in order to evaluate and process your application. If you request information or assistance from us, we may use the information you provide to fulfill your request.

We may also use the information you provide to contact you regarding your account and to process or collect payments. In addition, we may collect and use information for our own analytic, market research or marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

**Does CSBK  share the personal information you provide?**

We may share your information with service providers with whom we work to provide services to our customers as part of our daily operations.   When permitted or required by law, we may share information with additional third parties for other purposes including response to legal process. See our Privacy Notice for additional information on CSBK’s information sharing practices.

## Does CSBK use cookies or other technologies to collect information?

Like most other companies that maintain websites, when you browse or visit our Website, we may store certain information on your computer. This information may be in the form of a small text file called a "cookie" and can help us to tailor our Website to your individual preferences and save you time if you visit our Website again. 

_Can you disable or delete cookies?_   
You can disable cookies by making the appropriate selection from your browser options to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. However, if you choose to disable or delete cookies, you may limit the functionality of our Website. 

## Does CSBK track my online activity on its Website?

Like most other companies that maintain websites, we use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to help analyze the types of users who visit our Website and how users interact with our Website.  By using cookies, Google Analytics collects information, such as how often users visit websites, what sections or pages the user visits, and can identify other websites the user visited prior to coming to our Website.  The information generated by the cookie about your use of the CSBK Website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google Analytics. 

This information, in connection with information gathered from all other users of our Website, is used to compile statistical reports for CSBK use.  We will use this information as aggregate data to help us maintain our Website, to determine the number of visitors in total (and to different sections or pages of our Website), to ensure our Website is working properly, and to help us make our Website more relevant, accessible and useful. 

_CSBK, and any third party designee we may permit to access our Google Analytics data, will never use the Google Analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our Website_.  Furthermore, Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by CSBK, nor will Google link an IP address with the identity of an individual computer user.  We will not combine or associate any data gathered from our Website with any personally identifiable information from any source. 

Consumers who visit websites may opt out of Google Analytics Advertising Features. To do so:

  1. Visit the Network Advertising Initiative website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>
  2. Visit the Google Ads Help Center <https://support.google.com/ads/> and under How To, select Opt Out for detailed instructions.
  3. Download and install the Google Analytics opt-out add-on for your web browser at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

## How does CSBK protect information it collects via its Website?

We restrict access to the information obtained from our Website to only those employees, agents and contractors who need it to do their jobs. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect your information.

Additionally, companies that provide services on our behalf are required by contract to protect the information we collect. They are allowed to use the information we collect only for the purpose of providing the specific services we have contracted with them to provide.

## Does CSBK collect information about children via its Website?

Our Website is not intended for children under 13. We do not intentionally collect or maintain data about children under 13 unless the information is provided by a parent, legal guardian or authorized adult. 

## Will CSBK make changes to its Website Privacy Policy?

We reserve the right to alter this policy at our discretion. Any change to this policy will be posted on our Website in a timely manner.
